<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<notices>

  <error id="1000">
    <title>Bad syntax in the <ref to="header"/> header</title>
    <explain>Parse error: <ref to="error"/></explain>
  </error>

  <error id="1001">
    <title>Final <ref to="msg.headers.transfer_encoding"/> is not <tc>chunked</tc></title>
    <rfc num="7230" sect="3.3.1">
      If any transfer coding
   other than <tc>chunked</tc> is applied to a request payload body, the sender
   MUST apply <tc>chunked</tc> as the final transfer coding to ensure that the
   message is properly framed.
    </rfc>
  </error>

  <error id="1002">
    <title><ref to="msg.headers.transfer_encoding"/> contains <tc>chunked</tc> more than once</title>
    <rfc num="7230" sect="3.3.1">
      A sender MUST
   NOT apply <tc>chunked</tc> more than once to a message body (i.e., chunking an
   already chunked message is not allowed).
    </rfc>
  </error>

  <internal id="1003">
    <title>Not decoding <ref to="msg.headers.transfer_encoding"/>: <ref to="coding"/></title>
    <explain>HTTPolice does not know how to decode the <ref to="coding"/> transfer coding. (This doesn’t mean that it’s wrong.)</explain>
  </internal>

  <error id="1004">
    <title>Incomplete message according to <ref to="msg.headers.content_length"/></title>
    <explain>This message’s <ref to="msg.headers.content_length"/> header indicates that the body is <ref to="msg.headers.content_length.value"/> bytes long, but there are fewer bytes remaining on the stream.</explain>
  </error>

  <error id="1005">
    <title>Malformed <ref to="msg.headers.transfer_encoding"/>: <tc>chunked</tc></title>
    <explain>Parse error: <ref to="error"/></explain>
  </error>

  <error id="1006">
    <title>Malformed request heading</title>
    <explain>Parse error: <ref to="error"/></explain>
  </error>

  <internal id="1007">
    <title>Stop parsing request stream due to errors</title>
    <explain>Due to previous errors, the request stream is in an undefined state at this point, and HTTPolice will not try to parse the remaining bytes.</explain>
  </internal>

  <error id="1008">
    <title>Not enough requests for this response</title>
    <explain>If HTTPolice is parsing things correctly, it seems that there is no request corresponding to this response. HTTPolice will check this response in isolation.</explain>
  </error>

  <error id="1009">
    <title>Malformed response heading</title>
    <explain>Parse error: <ref to="error"/></explain>
  </error>

  <internal id="1010">
    <title>Stop parsing response stream due to errors</title>
    <explain>Due to previous errors, the response stream is in an undefined state at this point, and HTTPolice will not try to parse the remaining bytes.</explain>
  </internal>

  <internal id="1011">
    <title>Stop parsing response stream after switching protocols</title>
    <explain>The response status code <ref to="msg.status"/> indicates that the connection has switched to a different protocol. HTTPolice will not parse the remainder of the response stream.</explain>
  </internal>

  <internal id="1012">
    <title>Stop parsing response stream after switching to a tunnel</title>
    <explain>A successful (<ref to="msg.status"/>) response to a <ref to="msg.request.method"/> request indicates that the connection has switched to being a tunnel. HTTPolice will not parse the remainder of the response stream.</explain>
  </internal>

  <error id="1013">
    <title><ref to="entries">Multiple</ref> <ref to="header"/> headers</title>
    <rfc num="7230" sect="3.2.2">
      A sender MUST NOT generate multiple header fields with the same field
   name in a message unless either the entire field value for that
   header field is defined as a comma-separated list [i.e., #(values)]
   or the header field is a well-known exception (as noted below).
    </rfc>
  </error>

  <comment id="1014">
    <title>RWS is not a single space in <ref to="place"/></title>
    <explain>The specification for <ref to="place"/> includes the rule named RWS. It should be generated by senders as just a single space, but here it was <ref to="num"/> characters. See <rfc num="7230" sect="3.2.3"/>.</explain>
  </comment>

</notices>
